Hello hello everyone how are you all I am
your own personal artist Amit Raj Sharma and
you are watching this real In today's video
we will share with you the details of three variants of Lemon Pass Help Them Pension Plan
because we had already made a video in
which its fourth variant is named
Family First, we have already shared its information
This plan is a one point health
insurance policy in which you
also get protection of 119.
Talking about the category, this plan is
available in both individual and family floater categories The policy term is
one year along with the second year is also available,
meaning if someone wants to take a plan with one year, two year policy system, then a
discount of up to 12.5% ​​can be availed on the premium The
entry limit is
from 18 years to no limit but because there
is an option of up to ₹100 in it If you
go for higher sum insured then there will be pre
medical test, this thing is understood by a family  There are
variants in the plan of the head, in variant one there is an
option of Jasmin Side which is 2 lakh 34
lakh, in variant two the sum insured
option is 5 lakh, 7.5 lakh, 10 lakh
and 12.5 lakh in variant three there is 15 lakh,
20 lakh, 30 lakh for 50 people and up to 1 crore
time to see the interest option,
free hospitalization
is covered in all the variants, now to the award single
such private room which you can easily get
within 3 minutes, but if you
go for the state degree then you will get to
see the typing there, inside variant one,
along with this
you get cover of free hospitalization which is TDS,
free hospitalization
means whatever medical cost is incurred due to our
illness due to which we have to be
hospitalized, post
hospitalization means whatever
medical expenses are proved after discharge,
you get cover for seven days, there
is organ donor back cover.
Transplantation also falls under three categories,
you get it in short, you get it
undercover. When it comes to
ambulance expenses, then there
is a limit of up to ₹3000 in all three categories.
Now, when it comes to animal white
like German dog, if we take it sitting, then
its vaccination is undercover.
In all three variants, Vent One has a
limit of up to ₹5000, in One Two there is a limit of up to ₹5000, that is,
limited to 5000 and
in Valentine there is a limit of up to 7500 rupees.
Alternative treatment is
treatment in these variants. Now you all here
and you get it undercover.
Hospitalization is also back covered inside. Now let's
understand this. See, there is a patient who
cannot be taken to the hospital
and in such a situation, the medical experts are
ready to treat him at home. They are
also doing roadways or if there is no room available in the hospital or a
bed is not available, then
in that condition,  Hospitalization happens at home,
experts say that treatment can be done at home, then
you
get half a spoon of Ashwagandha in all events, that
recharge benefit also, you
get Aniruddha cover in 3 elections, if we talk about checkup, then if you
take a policy for 2 years in variant one, then you will get it once, in variant 2013
you can also get help facility on annual basis,
depending on the relationship,
sonth, no claim bonus, you can get from 20% to
100% of your sum insured, you can get
modern treatment like
robotic surgery etc. In this you get
limited up to one lakh rupees, hospital cash benefit in all variants,
which is optional,
you can take this option in variant one at the rate of ₹1000 per day in variant one, you can take it at the
rate of ₹2000 per day in variant two or you can take Moksha,
in variant four
you can take optional cover of hospital cash benefit up to 4000 per day,
now in this they have save good
writer, that is riders  It has been named
apple juice. You have more than one
benefit in it which you can avail according to your needs.
First is claim.
What is happening in Bardoli, us ghat, if there is a
non-verbal item, then there is a list of it,
that is half a teaspoon of dry ginger which is covered under it.
Second is no claim bonus. Shivgarh. Even if the policy goes up
to Rs 50,000 in the policy year, there will be no
impact on the no claim bonus benefits.
If you take this option, which we are
talking about, no claim bonus save guard. Third,
what happens in this is that
as you keep following it, your understanding will keep
increasing according to the inflation rate. There
is also an option of deductible ranging from Rs 1 lakh to Rs
10 lakh. Along with all the options, the
health checkup which you will
get for free, its cost can be reversed.
Although if you had to get it done in these network hospitals, then
all these tests of Kidnap Oscar, which you can read for this,
which also includes kidney function test,
so one thing you do not understand,
others also do not understand.  I want to explain that insurance provides
protection and protection is never taken incomplete.
You suggested us by commenting
that we should talk on this topic and
make a video on it. Thank you from the bottom of my heart for this
and if you want to know the information then you will get
its update on Telegram channel.